my Throne is where I say it
is I could have run OverWatch much
better than you and what would you have
done differently I would have caught all
the bad guys then cut their heads off H
tempting have you got a hamster in that
Mech um no sure sure I'm watching you
didn't I say I'd rip out your tongue if
I saw you again my queen your voice ever
sonorous is like a gentle waterfall upon
my ears right after the mission mark my
words yeah the ears are
next so I'm trying to ask everybody this
what is your favorite animal is there a
kind of dingo that is also a shark uh
yeah I can see it
they make them all as big as you where
you come from nah I was a special
order there's nothing about you in my
files no images no documents nothing
yeah well I'm what's the word starts
with e enigmatic that's the one and
don't you forget
it you look like a Bruiser want to be my
bodyguard huh I think you can take care
of
yourself I've met mozes with more brains
than you FKS with all the respect my
lady I believe that's a knock against
the junker Town education system we've
got an education
system Mo the Wreckers want you back
thought you might like to
know they'll hate that I'll pass it
along
I fought a bunch of you Bastion once you
all had wheels and big sharp
teeth on second thought that might have
been a dream I
[Music]
had anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table not unless you
want that table broken over your
head ain't easy is it being in charge of
killers and Mad Men no but I welcome the
challenge we got a lot in common shame
I'm going to kill you
someday
indeed where do I sign up for the
scrapyard fresh meat hey I'll try not to
bore me was just going to say the
same Genji remember the time you tripped
over your sword in training H some Ninja
it only happened once once was enough
what's the biggest ax you could make out
of hard light a kilometer tall but you
would not be able to wield it maybe you
wouldn't have I seen you before it's
possible I've passed through junon once
or twice you're the one who kicked red
Ned in the Wicker Basket he started
it my exquisitus queen I come bearing
news of great import not now rat junk my
name's junkrat now it
isn't J I need you to make me something
else a robot guard dog from your dirt
Garden maybe it can fly you decide a
suit of armor right but one that shouts
my name I need a slot bucket that's
bulletproof and don't you dare ask why a
grenade launcher with one trigger three
barrels paint glitter and no s he says
fine but give me a challenge next
time are you on average more mechanical
or more human why trying to figure out
whether to scrap you for parts H
consider the rail gun before you
decide I hear you'd like to pray on
omnic try me no thanks fought a bunch of
you before you're a bit gimmicky no
offense gimicky I said no
offense how many widows have you made
roughly I do not keep track well I'm
pretty sure I'm ahead